Utku Enes GÜRSEL

Selcuk University Faculty of Technology Computer Engineering GitHub

Hürriyet Mah. Abdi İpekçi Cad. Gökhan St. No.:35/4 Kartal / İstanbul (+90) 544 320 54 55 uenesgursel@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am a JavaScript developer focusing on Backend most of my time but I consider myself a Full Stack Developer.

I have developed and I am still developing with TypeScript on the Frontend and the Backend.

On the backend Node.js is my go to technology but I can learn other languages for another backend system such as python or golang, I have developed with both GraphQL and REST Api currently trying to shift to Type Graphql and get more experienced on TypeOrm.

On the Frontend React and Vue Frameworks are my favorites. I Have worked with SQL based Databases such as Postgres and MySQL, And I have experience building apps with NOSQL Databases such as MongoDB and Google Firestore, I Have used Serverless Technologies such as Google Firebase and build applications with it. I have the most experience with MERN Stack.

EXPERIENCE

Serin Trailer, Konya/Türkiye - Full Stack Developer

DECEMBER 2021- Still

Developing Companies CRM Application with Node.js and React.js

Serin Trailer, Konya/Türkiye - IT Support Expert(Part Time)

SEPTEMBER 2021- DECEMBER 2021

Working with 50-60 Computers. Company's server and Website. Networking to basic computer maintenance, Website adjustments to suit Company's needs.

VATAN Bilgisayar, Maltepe/İstanbul - Satış Temsilcisi

MAY 2018 - JUNE 2018

Save money and to have experience working and making my own money before going to University.

SKILLS

TypeScript
Javascript
GraphQL
TypeORM
Swift
React.js
Node.js
Dart/ Flutter
Github
SQL
No-SQL

Basketball Violin

EFSET English Certificate
79/100 (C2 Proficient)

LANGUAGES

Turkish - Native English - C2 Japanese - JLPT N1 German - B1

REFERENCES

Adil Kürşat BERBEROĞLU Serin Trailer International Representative Number: +90554 831 01 76 kursat.berberoglu@serin.com.tr

EDUCATION

Selçuk University, Konya / Turkey - Computer Enginnering

Actively attending - 2018 -

Majoring Computer Engineering, which is E.E. with Comp Sci.

E.C.A Elginkan Anatolian High School, Maltepe/İstanbul - 88,06/100

2014- 2018

Learned little bit of German and Played in the Volleyball team. Math , Physics , Chemistry , Biology ,German , English and Geometry are some of the classes I have taken over the four years.

PROJECTS

CRM Application

Tech Stack: React.js Node.js Express Mysql on Ubuntu 20.03 with Nginx

Designed and developed the app from scratch and deployed in our own server with nginx and Ubuntu. Front-end code is in a repo in my <u>GitHub</u>. Used JWT Tokens for a custom Authentication system.